The Moderator is a action, thriller, drama film directed by Zhor Fassi-Fihri.
After the murder of her two Scandinavian friends in Morocco, a
Russian blogger decides to do her own justice.
Mya Snik, played by Irma Lake.
Agent Richard Bourdeau, played by Gary Dourdan.
Agent John Ross, played by Robert Knepper.
Vance Wilhorn, played by Michael Patrick Lane.
Jawad, played by Brice Bexter.
Kenza, played by Maria-Claudia Nova.
The Lost City is a 2022 American action-adventure comedy film directed by Aaron and Adam Nee, who
co-wrote the screenplay with Oren Uziel and Dana Fox, based on a story by Seth Gordon.
Starring Sandra Bullock, Channing Tatum, Daniel Radcliffe, Da'Vine Joy Randolph and Brad Pitt, the film follows a romance novelist and her
cover model, who must escape a billionaire who wants her to find a lost ancient burial chamber described in one of her books.
The project was announced in October 2020 with Bullock joining as producer and star and Tatum
joining that December; the rest of the cast was announced the following year.
Filming took place in the Dominican Republic from May to August 2021.
The film premiered at South by Southwest on March 12, 2022, and was theatrically
released by Paramount Pictures in the United States on March 25, 2022.
It received generally positive reviews from critics and grossed over
$190 million worldwide against a $68 million budget.
The tone is emotional and intense.